Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
1891-2000
PricewaterhouseCoopers LLP.
148 linear feet (98 record cartons and 4 flat boxes).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library New York, NY. 10027
6898059
The collection is clearly divided into two record groups: Coopers & Lybrand archival materials and Price Waterhouse & Co. archival materials. The documents from the offices Price Waterhouse & Co. materials include original company documents, accounting books, and other records created by Price Waterhouse or the firms that have subsequently merged with it.
Historical Note
PricewaterhouseCoopers, one of the world's top accountancy firms, has been created in 1998 by the merger of two companies - Price Waterhouse and Coopers & Lybrand - each with historical roots going back some 150 years to the 19th century Great Britain. The collection of PWC archival materials, donated to Columbia University in 2000, traces the rise of both companies to major worldwide professional services powerhouses through mergers and business expansion.
In the1890s both companies established their presence in the United States. The American accounting as a profession was then a new undertaking with limited experience, little or no organized training facilities and practically no authoritative means of establishing and enforcing professional standards. Early founders of both firms were deeply involved in professional organizations of the time and instrumental in establishing the standards and terminology of the nascent accounting profession. By maintaining a firm stand on matters of professional ethics, and by relying on British practice and precedent, these accountants played an important role in developing American auditing standards. Influenced by market environment, legislative decisions and technological advances, Price Waterhouse & Co. and Coopers & Lybrand were, to a large extent, developing along similar lines.
Price Waterhouse & Co.: In 1850 Samuel Lowell Price sets up his accounting business in London. In 1865 he was joined in partnership by William H. Holyland and an Edwin Waterhouse and by 1874 the company name changes to Price, Waterhouse & Co. In 1873, the firm conducted their first US project. The growing US practice lead to the establishment of permanent PW presence in the Western hemispere, which began with the opening of the office on 45 Broadway, New York City in 1890 by a company agent Lewis D. Jones. He was soon joined in America by William J. Caesar, who opened an office in Chicago. In 1895 the newly created Jones, Caesar & Co. was designated as an agent of Price Waterhouse. After Jones early death Arthur L. Dickinson replaced retiring Caesar as a senior partner of the American firm.
The firm enjoyed solid reputation and high business volume. By the turn of the century, it built up a roster of clients which covered a wide range of industrial and commercial fields in most sections of the country. Branch offices began to open throughout the USA and then in other parts of the world: 1907 Joseph E. Sterett, an American with his own successful practice, joins the company and the American firm's name changed from Jones, Caesar, Dickinson, Wilmot & Co. to Dickinson, Wilmot & Sterret. By Dickinson's retirement as a senior partner in 1911 the firm grows large enough to need the committee structure. In 1913 the name of American firm is dropped in favor of the English name Price Waterhouse & Co.
The 100 years of Price Waterhouse history in America divide into three periods, each characterized by its own problems and dilemmas (McDermott and Allen, p. 248). The first era (1890s to late 1920s) saw the Americanization of the practice and the rise of the firm around professionally automonous partners. The second era, from the early 1930s to the late 1960s marked the dominance of PW in the regulated monolithic environment in which the accounting profession then functioned. The securities laws of the early 1930s pushed the audit to the center of firms' practice. During the 'golden age' of 1950s the flow of capital to Europe led PW to establish the international firm. The same time period witnessed the start of series of mergers at home. The third era, 1970 to 1990s, saw the reformulation of the agenda in a period of radical change in both marketplace and the profession. 1982 Price Waterhouse World Firm formed. The steady absorbtion of the more successful local and regional practices in the Big Eight (later Big Six) accelerated. Innovations in technology resulted in changes to traditional work pattern. Shifting client base, wave of litigations, changes in service mix and additional standards, established by SEC and Congress, led to increase in overhead costs. All these factors eroded industry structure established in 1930s. Greater competitiveness led to dismantling of earlier professional prohibitions against advertizing. Price competition in audit wars, and industry mergers led Price Waterhouse, which always focues on auditing, to start admitting non-CPA's and expand management consulting services.
Coopers & Lybrand: In 1854 William Cooper establishes his own practice in London, which seven years later becomes Cooper Brothers. Firm's history in the United States begins in 1898, when Robert H. Montgomery, William M. Lybrand, Adam A. Ross Jr. and his brother T. Edward Ross form Lybrand, Ross Brothers and Montgomery in Philadelphia. During the early 20th century, their offices spread around the country and then in Europe. The explosive growth ended with Great Depression that forced the firm to reorganize organizational structure, and to shift the focus from expansion toward flexible specialization, such as finding new types of services (tax services, management consulting) for exhisting clientele. In the 1930s LRB&M was enegaged by the federal government to investigate several banks and trust ocmpanies throughout the United States - the work of unprecedented magnitude, ranging from an investigation to a detailed audit followed by liquidation proceedings.
After the death of Col. Montgomery in 1953, the new generation of leaders came to the fore: Alvin R. Jennings, Walter A. Staub, Philip L. Defliese, Norman E. Auerbach. Under their leadership, the firm experienced a major transformation from medium-size company, focused on auditing and primarliy national in scope, into a multinational player with a growing mix of consulting services. The boldest step was a 1957 merger between Cooper Brothers & Co (UK), McDonald, Currie and Co (Canada) and Lybrand, Ross Bros & Montgomery (US), forming Coopers & Lybrand - a truly international powerhouse, operating through 79 offices in 19 countries. 1950s also saw the addition of an autonomous line of specialization in mamagement consulting services. The company acquired more formal oragnizational structure, and continued a policy of selective mergers, including an important addition of Scovell, Vellington & Co. in 1962. In 1973 American firm adopts the name Coopers and Lybrand. Globalization and information boom led to increased interest in Knowledge Management, adding it to the existing mix of professional services. In 1990 Coopers & Lybrand merges with Deloitte Haskins & Sells in a number of countries around the world In 1998 Price Waterhouse and Coopers & Lybrand merge worldwide to become PricewaterhouseCoopers.
Scope and Content
The collection is clearly divided into two record groups: Price Waterhouse & Co. archival materials and Coopers & Lybrand archival materials. The documents from the offices Price Waterhouse & Co. materials include original company documents, accounting books, and other records created by Price Waterhouse or the firms that have subsequently merged with it. The group further contains papers of George O. May, (led the company from 1911 to 1926), files from the office of Herman W. Bevis (led the company from 1961 to 1969), company publications and library of book related to accounting. This group also includes the files of historical research conducted by Winthrop Group for Centennial of Price Waterhouse in America (1990), oral history tapes and transcripts, videos and digital materials.
Coopers and Lybrand materials include original company documents, accounting books, and other records created by Lybrand, Ross Brothers & Montgomery, Coopers Brothers and other firms that have subsequently merged to form Coopers and Lybrand. A large collection of printed materials contains first editions, manuals, broshures and periodicals. Also included are files and audio recordings of James Mahon (LRB&;M National Director of Practice Development), and files from the office of Catherine "Millie" McGovern, C&;L manager and event coordinator. Numerous audiovisual materials include photos, video documentaries and oral history records. This record group also includes historical research conducted by the Business History Group for CL centennial (1998).
Arrangement
In two sequences: Coopers & Lybrand and Price Waterhouse.
Coopers & Lybrand Series I: Cataloged originals
Coopers & Lybrand Series II: Printed materials
Coopers & Lybrand Series III: Photographs
Coopers & Lybrand Series IV: Audio Records
Coopers & Lybrand Series V: Microflim
Coopers & Lybrand Series VI: Digital files
Coopers & Lybrand Series VII: Moving Image
Coopers & Lybrand Series VIII: Art and Ephemera
Coopers & Lybrand Series IX: Books and Monographs
Price Waterhouse Series I: Cataloged Documents
Price Waterhouse Series II: Printed Matter
Price Waterhouse Series III: Photographs and Art
Price Waterhouse Series IV: Audio
Price Waterhouse Series V: Moving Image
Price Waterhouse Series VI: Digital files
Price Waterhouse Series VII: Books and Monographs
Subjects
Lybrand, Ross Bros. & Montgomery.; PricewaterhouseCoopers LLP.; Mahon, James Joseph, 1912-; Accounting.; Accounting--Law and legislation.; Auditing.; Auditing, Internal.; Corporations--Taxation--Law and legislation.; Commercial law.; Income tax--Law and legislation.; Taxation--Law and legislation.
Access Restrictions
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Acquisition
The PWC Archive was donated to Columbia University by PriceWaterhouseCoopers in August 2000.
The documents from the offices Price Waterhouse & Co. have been collected by Price Waterhouse Library and Information Center, with additions from May family, files from the office of H. W. Bevis and historical research files from Winthrop Group. Coopers and Lybrand materials include records created by Lybrand, Ross Brothers & Montgomery, Coopers Brothers and other firms that have subsequently merged to form Coopers & Lybrand. James Mahon files were donated to Coopers & Lybrand by Mahon family. Audiovisual materials and large collection of first editions and periodicals was collected by the C&;L librarian and then preserved by Catherine "Millie" McGovern, C&;L manager and event coordinator. Historical research files for CL centennial (1998) were created by The Business History Group.
- Coopers & Lybrand Series I: Cataloged originals
  Contains early documents on the Firm's history (singly and in scrapbooks), early bookkeeping.
  - Subseries I.1: Account Books
    - Sub-subseries I.1.1: Bound Volumes
      Bound Volumes of formal bookkeeping records with handwritten entries
      - LRB&M Journal, Philadelphia Office, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1919 - Sep. 1929, 160p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - LRB&M Journal, Philadelphia Office, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1929 - Sep. 1937, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Journal, Philadelphia Office, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1937 - Sep. 1943, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - LRB&M Journal, [Philadelphia Office], [Philadelphia, PA], Oct. 1943 - Apr. 1952, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - LRB&M Journal, n.p., Dec. 31 1918 - Sep. 30, 1923, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - LRB&M Journal, n.p., May 1952 - Mar. 1959, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - LRB&M Journal, n.p., Apr. 1959 - Mar. 1964, 152p. (10.5 x 8.5 x 0.5) (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - LRB&M Journal No.2, n.p., Dec. 31 1909 - Mar. 17, 1920, 200p, 47p used (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - LRB&M Journal No.3, n.p., Dec. 31 1911 - Sep. 30, 1919, 200p, 86p used (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - LRB&M Journal No.4, n.p., Apr. 1924 - Sep. 1929, 200p. (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - LRB&M Journal No.5, n.p., Oct. 2, 1935 - Sep. 30, 1930, 300p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - LRB&M Journal No.6, Philadelphia, PA, 1898 - 1909, 129p. (14 x 9 x 1) (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - LRB&M Journal No.7, n.p., 1908 - [1920], 188p. (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - LRB&M Journal No.8, n.p., 1911 - 1913, 192p. (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - LRB&M Journal No.9, n.p., 1914 - 1915, 172p. (11 x 8.5 x 1) (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Journal No.10, n.p., 1916 - 1917, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - LRB&M Journal No.11, n.p., 1918, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - LRB&M Journal No.12, n.p., 1919 - 1920, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - LRB&M Journal No.13, Philadelphia, PA, 1919 - Sep.30, 1924, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - LRB&M Journal No.14, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1924 - Sep. 30, 1927, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - LRB&M Journal No.15, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1927 - Sep. 30, 1929, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - LRB&M Journal No.16, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1929 - Sep. 30, 1932, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - LRB&M Journal No.17, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1932 - Sep. 30, 1936, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - LRB&M Journal No.18, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1936 - Sep. 30, 1939, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Journal No.19, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1939 - Sep. 30, 1941, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - LRB&M Journal No.20, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1941 - Sep. 30, 1943, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - LRB&M Journal No.21, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1943 - Sep. 30, 1950, 372p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - LRB&M Journal No.22, Philadelphia, PA, Oct. 1, 1950 - [1956], 400p. (11 x 9 x 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - LRB&M Journal No.23, n.p., Oct. 1, 1920 - Sep. 20, 1924, 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - LRB&M Journal No.24, n.p., Oct. 1, 1924 - [1929], 272p. (11 x 9 x 1.5) (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - LRB&M Journal No.25, n.p., 1956 - 1959, approx. 150 (unbound) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Journal No.26, n.p., 1956 - 1960, approx. 100 (unbound) (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - LRB&M Journal No.27, n.p., 1920 - 1925 (Box 346, Folder 1)
        [Oversized]
      - LRB&M Journal No.28, n.p., 1898 - 1901, 252p. (14 x 9 x 1) (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - LRB&M Journal No.29, n.p., 1898 - 1909, 303p. (14 x 9 x 1) (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - LRB&M Journal No.30, n.p., 1898 - 1900, c. 300p. (10 x 6 x 1) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries I.1.2: Individual Documents
      Arranged Chronologically
      - Snyder, Benjamin P., president National Safe Deposit Company to: John Heins commending Mr. Ross, Washington, DC, Aug. 28, 1891, 1p. (a.l.s.) (Box 4, Folder 7)
        [Mounted]
      - Financial Sheet, n.p., Feb. 1895, 2p. (a.d.) (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Heins, Lybrand & Co Partnership agreement and business card, Philadelphia, PA, Apr. 16, 1986, 3p. (t.d.s.), 1 (card) (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Financial Sheet, n.p., [1986], 1p. (a.d.) (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Girard Life Insurance Annuity and Trust Company Checks No. 1 & 2 signed by Lybrand, Ross Bros & Montgomery, Philadelphia, PA, Jan. 31, 1898, 2 (d.s.) (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - LRB&M Partnership agreement, signed by William Lybrand, Adam Ross, Edward Ross, Robert Montgomery, Philadelphia, PA, Apr. 7, 1898, 1p. (t.d.s.) (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - LRB&M Auditor's Notebook. Client - University of Pensylvania, Philadelphia, PA, 1902, 23p. (Notebook) (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - LRB&M Memorandum on reporting time, n.p., Jul. 26, 1905, 1p. (t.d.s.) (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - LRB&M Partnership agreement, signed by William Lybrand, Adam Ross, Edward Ross, Robert Montgomery, Joseph Pugh, n.p., Dec. 31, 1908; Dec. 31, 1910, 2 (t.d.s.) (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - John Wood Jr. Sherwood Distilling Company, Baltimore, MD, Apr. - Jul. 1910, 80p. (Diary) (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - U.S. Internal Revenue Service Individual Income Tax Return - First Form 1040, 1913, 4p. (Government Document) (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - LRB&M Minutes of Firm Meetings, Philadelphia, PA, 1914 - 1940, 268p. (t.d.), 2 (a.note) (Box 4, Folder 17A)
      - LRB&M Memorandum on reporting time, n.p., Jan. 19, 1920, 1p. (t.d.) (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - LRB&M Invitation, Memo, program and menu relating to Staff Dinner at Bellevue-Stratford Hotel, Philadelphia, PA, Apr. 17, 1920, 1p. (t.d.), 8p. (Program/menu) (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - LRB&M Invitation, Memo, program and menu relating to Staff Dinner at The Biltmore, NY, New York, NY, Apr. 17, 1920, 2p. (card) (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - LRB&M List of Powers of Attourney filled with Treasury Department, Washington DC, [1921 - 1965], 2 volumes (9 x 6 x 0.5, alphabetized notebook) (Box 4, Folder 21)
        [Vol. 2 needs repair]
      - Pennsylvania Institute of Certified Public Accountants Invitation, program and menu relating to PA ICPA 25th Anniversary Dinner, Philadelphia, PA, Dec. 8, 1922, 2p. (card), 2p. (menu), 2p. (program) (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - LRB&M Invitation, Memo, program and menu relating to Staff Dinner at The Biltmore, New York, NY, Jan. 6, 1923, 2p. (card) (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - LRB&M Letter No. 18 to members in US Armed Forces, n.p., 25-May-45, 1p. (t.d.) (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Ross, Howard P.S. Ross & Sons to: Leete, Harry O., Esq, LRB&M New York, Montreal, Canada, Oct. 31, 1949, 2p. (t.l.s.), 1p. (photostat negative print) (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - American Institute of Accountants Resolution on death of Robert Montgomery, Chicago, IL, 1953, booklet) (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Cooper Brothers & Co. Centennial Declaration, n.p., 1954, 1 (Original), 1 (Copy) (Box 346, Folder 2)
      - Chemical Bank and Trust LRB&M New York 25th Anniversary Lucheon invitation & menu, New York, NY, Sep. 20, 1954, 2p. (card) (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - LRB&M Annual Firm Meeting, Pocono, PA, Oct. 3 - 7, 1970, 4p. (program) (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Defliese, Philip L. LRB&M Memorandum on name change to Coopers & Lybrand, New York, NY, Jan. 8, 1973, 1p. (t.d.s.), 1p. (d.) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Sub-subseries I.1.3: Scrapbooks
      Scrapbooks contain announcements such as: company services, new offices and partners, address and staff changes, mergers, anniversary selebration, death notices. Most documents are off the original pages, due to the aging of the glue. Glue and scotch tape traces on most documents. Cards mostly have a second copy on file (count represents number of distinct items)
      - LRB&M Announcements, 1909 - 1930, 40 (cards), 2 (pamphlets/broshures), 5 (t.l.), clippings (photocopies)) (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - LRB&M Announcements and ads, 1931 -1993, 40 (cards), 18 (clippings (photocopies)), 3 (t.d.) (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - LRB&M Announcements and ads, 1947 - 1960, 38 (cards), 31 (clippings (photocopies)), 2 (t.d.) (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - LRB&M LRB&M to C&L Scrapbook, 1924 - 1958, 4 (cards), 4 (Legal Documents), 20 (t.l.), clippings ) (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Scrapbook pages used for Centennial Research, 1924 - 1960, 18 (cards), 3 (clippings (photocopies)) (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Scovell, Wellington & Co. Announcements, 1923 - 1961, 56 (cards), 5p. (clippings (photocopies)), 3 (t.d.) (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Scovell, Wellington & Co. Bulletines: Index for Vols. I & II, 16p. (t.d.) (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Scovell, Wellington & Co. Bulletines: Vol. I, 1915 - 1952, 3 (cards), 56 (pamphlets/broshures), 12 (charts), t.d.) (Box 5, Folder 6 - 8)
      - Scovell, Wellington & Co. Bulletines: Vol. I I, 1915 - 1952, 1 (cards), 45 (pamphlets/broshures), 1 (charts) (Box 5, Folder 9 - 10)
      - C&L International Firm Meeting, Boston, MA, Oct. 1979, 23 (cards), 8 (Charts), 7 (t.d.), 7 (pamphlets/broshures), 6 (registration forms) (Box 346, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries I.1.4: Bound documents
      Bound volumes contain original correspondence and typed papers
      - Pennsylvania Institute of Certified Public Accountants Papers read at 25th Anniversary dinner, Philadelphia, PA, Dec. 8, 1922, 87 pages (t.d.) (Box 5, Folder 11 - 12)
        [2 copies]
      - LRB&M World War II: Letters to Members of the Staff and Office Force in the Military Service. Philadelphia, PA, 1942 - 1946, 210 (t.l.) (Box 5, Folder 13)
        [2 copies, bound]
      - LRB&M Fiftieth Anniversary Acknowledgements. Vol 1: A - K; List of signatures and affiliations enclosed., New York, 1948 - 1949, 202 (t. l. s.) (Box 6, Folder 1)
        [bound]
      - LRB&M Fiftieth Anniversary Acknowledgements. Vol. 2 - L-Z. List of signatures and affiliations enclosed., New York, 1948 - 1949, 222 (t. l. s.) (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - LRB&M Fiftieth Anniversary Acknowledgements. Vol 3, Boston, 1949, 242 (t. l. s.) (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - LRB&M Fiftieth Anniversary Acknowledgements. Vol 4 - out of town, except Boston, 1949, 327 (t. l. s.) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Subseries I.2: Centennial Research
    C&L 100th Anniversary Celebration (1998) and book (Building Values and Traditions: 100 Years of Coopers & Lybrand) project. Research work conducted by Business History Group, Inc.
    - Subsubseries I.2.1: Firm History files
      General information and celebration guidelines
      - Anniversaries and Special Events Guide, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Book Design and Budget Proposal, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Research guides and correspondence, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - C&L Publications from Hibbert Group, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence with Retired Partners, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Copies of Historical Documents, 1930s - 1970s. (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Philadelphia Office Materials, 1920 - 1962 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Bertine, Dorothy Firm History, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Smith, Tony Firm History, n.d (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Virtual Volunteers, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - History and Structure of Firm Council, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Sub-subseries I.2.2: Interviews and Biographies
      Conducted by Business History Group. Originals photos moved to Photographs series, replaced by xerox copies.
      - Amhowitz, Harris; Bolz, Norman; Burd, Roger; Burnett, Donald; Clarke, James; Collins, Bernhardt W.; Crosby Jr., Ralph R.; Cranz, Russell K.; Dyer, Donald E.; Francis, Kerry L.; Goldfein, Iris D.; Hahn, Maurice S.; Harteneck, Guillermo (Bill), Herr, Fred G.; Hobart, Lawrence C.; Hunt, Alfred L.; Jones, Seymour; Kaufman, Felix; Keast, William B.; Knapp, Ellen M; Landry, Horace J; McKessy, Stephen W.; Maheu, Ronald T.; Martin, Anthony F; Meredith, Ted; Metcalf, Richard; Moore, Nicholas G; Morrow, Beate (Bea) M.; Mozenter, Gary; Nelson, Gail; O'Brien, William K.; O'Reilly, Vincent M.; Padgett, John C.; Petty, Glenn O.; Pomeranz, Felix. Questionnaires and Biographical Info: A - P (Box 7, Folder 1)
        [Photos removed from: Crosby, Ralph]
      - Rappaport, Louis H.; Roberts, John J.; Schroeder, Donald W.; Stewart, Cliff; Tasch, Raymond C.; Warner, Robert S.; Waters, Robert K.; Wellington, Roger; Williams, Kenneth D.; Yost III, George J. (Jay); Zug, Harry C. Questionnaires and Biographical Info: R - Z (Box 7, Folder 2)